http://www.mncee.org/privacy-policy/

Home /
Are you on the list?
Don't miss a beat! Join our mailing list for quarterly news and updates on CEE's programs, research, resources, and services.
More
Privacy Policy
CEE is a non-profit organization whose mission is to discover and deploy the most effective energy solutions that strengthen the economy and improve the environment. CEE respects your privacy and strives to protect it through its compliance with this policy.
This policy applies to this website, and any other, CEE- hosted website. It also applies to information submitted by you when contacting us via our contact page or email submission.
Your Consent
We ask you to please take a few minutes to review this Policy before using this Site. By using this Site you are consenting to the collection, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information as set forth in this Policy. If you do not agree to be bound by this Policy, you may not access or use this Site. As our website is updated occasionally, so might our policy, so please check periodically for updates.
Children under 13
We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under age 13. We are proud of this Site and we strive to ensure that it does not offend people of any age. However, this Site is not intended for children or minors under the age of thirteen years without the permission of a parent or guardian.
Type of information we collect
Contact information
If you fill out our contact page or send us an email, you will be supplying us with information (such as your name, email address or physical address) that will enable us to identify and contact you. We may use this information for the completion and support of a specific request or to contact you in the way you've asked us to. We will not sell, rent or give this information to outside third parties.
Aggregate information
General, anonymous information about the visitors to all of our sites may be collected. This information may include pages visited, the computer platform and browser type used, how long pages are visited, whether the visitor has been to our site before, and the order of pages visited. This information is collected and reviewed in the aggregate and is not personally identifiable. The information is used to help us administer our site and to understand how visitors interact with our site so that we can continue to improve it. Your Web browser contains settings which can limit the amount of tracking a given website can do.  Please refer to your browser's help documentation or the manufacturer for more information.
Cookies
We may use cookies (small text files stored on your device) to help determine whether you've been to our site before and what pages you've visited. This information is not personally identifiable and is used to analyze trends, to administer our site and to help us improve them.
External links
If you follow any external links from our site to sites run by others, please understand that our privacy policy does not extend to those sites and CEE is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other sites. Access or update your information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given to:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Data security
CEE embraces industry standard data security practices and implements them wherever it is practical.  We protect company and personal data at rest and in transit using technology including but not limited to firewalls, anti-virus/anti-malware, access control lists/access permission, patch management, security scanning, and physical access to buildings, offices, & IT equipment.  We also conduct regular staff trainings and reviews of these policies & guidelines to promote transparent secure business practices.
Questions or complaints
If you have any questions about our policy, suggestions to help us improve it, or believe we have violated any aspect of it, please contact us at 612-335-5858 or administrative@mncee.org.
CEE
Minneapolis - Downtown
212 3rd Avenue North, Suite 560
Minneapolis, MN 55401
(612) 335-5858
St. Paul - Midway
1754 University Avenue West
St. Paul, MN 55104
Privacy Policy | Site Map    © 2020 Center for Energy and Environment
